<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-14T19:11:06-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Back Online</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/26/third-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Back Online" /><published>2018-08-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/08/26/third-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/08/26/third-post.html">&lt;p&gt;This is a new blog post to complain about what it’s like coming back to a task after having abandoned it for so long…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other thing that I am sick of is the constant images of kittens. No More!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Connolly</name></author><summary type="html">This is a new blog post to complain about what it’s like coming back to a task after having abandoned it for so long…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This is the title of the post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/05/29/second-blog-entry.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This is the title of the post" /><published>2018-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/05/29/second-blog-entry</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/05/29/second-blog-entry.html">&lt;p&gt;Dear bird resting in my hand
I so admire your golden plumage,
Such dramatic attire; documentaries claim
It’s part of your mating game, except out here in the
Swampy reeds along this churning river, where fishermen
Sometimes wade
There are few females to impress.
I wonder if you gild your feathers just for
Aesthetic pleasure?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>James Connolly</name></author><summary type="html">Dear bird resting in my hand I so admire your golden plumage, Such dramatic attire; documentaries claim It’s part of your mating game, except out here in the Swampy reeds along this churning river, where fishermen Sometimes wade There are few females to impress. I wonder if you gild your feathers just for Aesthetic pleasure?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This is the title of the post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/05/28/initial-blog-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This is the title of the post" /><published>2018-05-28T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-05-28T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/05/28/initial-blog-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/05/28/initial-blog-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Call me &lt;em&gt;Ishmael&lt;/em&gt;. Some years ago–&lt;em&gt;never mind how long
precisely&lt;/em&gt;–having little or no money in my purse, and nothing
particular to interest me on shore, I thought I would sail about a little
and see the watery part of the world. It is a way I have of driving off
the spleen and regulating the circulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;pull-left&quot; src=&quot;http://placekitten.com/g/400/200&quot; alt=&quot;kitten&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whenever I find myself growing grim about the mouth; whenever it is a damp,
drizzly November in my soul; whenever I find myself involuntarily pausing
before coffin warehouses, and bringing up the rear of every funeral I meet;
and especially whenever my hypos get such an upper hand of me, that it
requires a strong moral principle to prevent me from deliberately stepping
into the street, and methodically knocking people’s hats off—then, I
account it high time to get to sea as soon as I can. This is my substitute
for pistol and ball.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a philosophical flourish Cato throws himself upon
his sword; I quietly take to the ship. There is nothing surprising in this.
If they but knew it, almost all men in their degree, some time or other,
cherish very nearly the same feelings towards the ocean with me.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Me, Myself, and I</name></author><summary type="html">Call me Ishmael. Some years ago–never mind how long precisely–having little or no money in my purse, and nothing particular to interest me on shore, I thought I would sail about a little and see the watery part of the world. It is a way I have of driving off the spleen and regulating the circulation.</summary></entry></feed>